好吧 我个人经历过的最独特的驾驶体验之一
Alright so one of the most unique motoring experiences I've ever had
个人
personally
是我曾经的
was back
日常开特斯拉的时候
when I was daily driving a Tesla I got to drive
我试驾了2008年的特斯拉跑车
and borrow the original the Tesla Roadster from 2008
真正感受到了电动跑车的起点
and got to really feel the beginning
体会到了电动跑车本该有的感觉
and the experience of what original electric sports car was supposed to be
然后 自那之后的变化触手可及
and then obviously see the evolution that happened since then.
现在我日常开的是911
Now you know I'm daily driving a 911
我问的一个问题是
and The question I may have had is
类似的体验又会是什么样的呢？
what would an equivalent throwback experience be?
而这辆车 其实并没有看上去那么简单
And this one, it's actually not exactly what it looks like
你们可能在想 哎呀
because you're probably thinking, oh
你是说 你要开一辆手动的经典涡轮车吗？
you're going to drive a manual OG turbo?
那可是辆驾驶起来让人疯狂的车呀！
That's a crazy car to drive.
不 不是的
No, no, no, no, no.
这辆车 实际上是电动的
This one, this one's electric.
最近几天
So for the past couple of days
迈尔斯和我最近开这辆车 真的是一种享受
Miles and I have had a real treat driving around this thing.
这是款经过改装的964款保时捷911
This is a sort of remodeled 964 generation Porsche 911.
这辆车是由Sacrilege Motors公司完全改装成电动的
to be fully electric by a company called Sacrilege Motors
名字取得也是很有意思
probably appropriately named
因为很多人看到这一点时
because there's plenty of people who see this
看到电动汽车时觉得有些不妥
and see electric and that feels sacrilegious
但你可以看到评论
but then you see the reviews
以及人们对开这辆车的看法
and what people have thought about driving this thing
而似乎他们的表现非常出色
and Seems like they've done an incredible job.
所以我想去看看
So I just wanted to check it out
看看这车开起来怎么样
and see how this actually drove.
结果它是手动原始驾驶感与新动力系统的完美结合
And it turns out it's an incredible combination of the manual original feel
with this obviously new powertrain being
我敢说 这比原版更好
Well, I'll say it, better than the original.
如果你回去看看那段最初的
Now, if you go back and watch that original
2008年特斯拉跑车的视频
Living with the 2008 Tesla Roadster video,
你会看到
you'll see, I mean
这让人感受到一种浓厚的怀旧气息
it's quite a throwback from the Teslas of today.
屏幕小了许多
The screens are much smaller
汽车也小了许多
the car is much smaller
电池小了许多
the battery is much smaller
而且所有的东西都比较落后
and everything is just further behind.
它更偏向于模拟 但并不完全是
It's more analog, but not completely.
这一代车型最早出现在80年代
This generation car first came out in the 80s.
这是1989年的一款车型
It's a 1989 model.
所以这里没有任何屏幕
And so there were no screens.
这更像是一种重温往昔的感觉
This is even more of a throwback.
你可能会觉得和它一起生活可真疯狂
And so you might think living with it would be crazy.
然后把这些稀有的车开回来
And then taking one of these rare cars
而把它改造成电动车
and going through the work of turning it into an electric car is just
简直是一个疯狂的想法
a crazy idea.
不过 经过一段时间的使用
But after I've lived with it now
现在我真的懂人们为什么这么做了
I actually get why people do it.
在我的经历中 有些惊喜
And there may be some surprises in my experience
我现在就和大家分享
that I'll share with you now.
那我们就直接开始吧！
So let's just jump right in.
首先 这辆车太美了！
So first of all, gorgeous car.
我可能有偏见 因为我选择了
I might be biased because I'm obviously
这款受其启发的车
I chose a car that's inspired heavily by this
而且我还有一辆黑色的
and I actually have a black one too
但你可以看到这是宽体车型
but you can see this is the wide body one
而且它也是一辆敞篷车
and it's a convertible as well so cabriolet if you want to call it that
有个有趣的点：
and the thing to note here that's kind of interesting
这里有很多部件
is there's a lot of parts here
这些部件来自原版保时捷
that are shared from the original Porsche parts
还有很多新部件 比如这些轮子
but also a lot of new parts like you can see these wheels here
你可以看到这些新款的Brembo刹车几乎塞不进车轮下面
you also see these new Brembo brakes that barely fit underneath the wheels
而且他们还装上了Pilot Sport轮胎
and but they get in there pilot sport tires
几乎塞不进护翼的轮胎
that barely fit under the fenders
而且后面的轮胎也非常宽大
and these are some big wide tires back here too
这些是295宽、18英寸的轮圈
matter of fact what can i see these are 295 section 18 inch rims
后面的轮胎相当有劲
these are some juicy tires back here
尤其是考虑到这辆车的动力
for the amount of power this thing puts out
马力为500 扭矩为500牛米
which is 500 horsepower and 500 newton meters
现在 它已经是电动车了！
Now, it's electric
如今许多汽车的电池就安装在
so a lot of the cars built today have the batteries in
就像小滑板一样
like this little skateboard
车底下
underneath the car.
那这个车的电池在哪里呢？
But where's the battery in here?
其实这里有两个电池
There's actually two.
前面有一个大电池
Big one in the front
后面还有一个大电池
and big one in the back.
所以如果有机会的话
so on the off chance
你是在进行公路旅行
that you're doing a road trip
或者说 这辆车有一点前备箱空间
or something in this car you do have a little bit of front trunk space
但是不多
not a huge amount
但可以放下一个适配器 或者一个登机箱大小的包
but enough for an adapter maybe a bag a carry-on size bag or so
而那半块电池就藏在地毯下面
but that's half the battery right there below that carpeting
还有可调的减震器
also your adjustable dampers
我想那是你的挡风玻璃刮水器液
and i i think that's uh your windshield wiper fluid so there's
如此一来 重量的一半就在这里 后面是这个标志性的鸭尾
where half the weight goes So behind this iconic ducktail
原发电厂的位置有另一半电池
where the old power plant used to be there's the other half of the battery
当然 还有减震器
and of course your dampers as well
但那确实很重
but that is a whole bunch of weight
你可以看到 重量分布均匀
so now you can see it's kind of evenly distributed
这里没有额外储存空间
there's no more storage in here
前面和后面各有一半电池
but there's half the battery in the front half the battery in the back
这样的话 总共能让你行驶大约200英里
And in total, that's going to get you around 200 miles of range
如果正常驾驶 这辆车一次充电能行驶
on a single charge if you drive it like normal
这还挺令人印象深刻的
which is actually kind of impressive
因为这车真的很小
because of how small this car really is.
毕竟 这车没什么空间放电池
I mean, you don't expect a whole bunch of space to put battery in.
电池不在地板上
But since the battery is not on the floor
所以驾驶位置
that means the driving position
而且内饰比原版更接近了
and all this interior is closer than ever to the original.
这些是新座位
These are new seats.
当然
But then, of course
我进来的时候
when I get in here
你会看到许多原版保时捷 我记得这一点
you're going to see a whole bunch original Porsche so I remember
当我制作电动大众巴士时
when I made that video on the refreshed Volkswagen bus the electric one
ID Buzz 收到了很多
the ID buzz there was a lot
评论说这挺酷的
of comments that were like this is kind of cool
大概是这样
I guess
但我希望他们能还原那个旧的复古设计
but I wish they just took the exact old retro design
然后把它改成电动版
and they just made that one electric
而我现在完全明白了
and I totally get it now
因为这车基本上就是这样
because that's basically what this car is
我四周都是模拟部件 根本看不到屏幕
I am surrounded by analog parts not a single screen in sight
其实他们给我装了一个小屏幕 用于车载娱乐
well actually they've given me a little tiny screen here for car play
但这几乎算不上屏幕
and it barely counts as a screen
因为这个是额外加上去的
because this is added extra
但开车时 你只需专注于这个方向盘
but when you're driving you're focused here on this wheel
还有这精致的内饰
and on this beautiful interior
现在的仪表基本上就是这些 你之前看到的那个钥匙
which is basically just your gauges now you saw that key from before
这就是启动车的方法 把钥匙插进去 转一转
this is the way to turn the car on stick the key right in there turn it
你会看到这些仪表转动 显示也都更新了
and you see these gauges spin up so the gauges are of course updated
以适应这辆车的电动特性
a bit to work with the electric nature of this car
所以它在显示我的电池电量
so it's telling me my battery level
它还会告知我
It's also going to tell me
我现在的驾驶模式
which drive mode I'm in
我正在使用多少电力
how much power I'm using.
音效不错
Great sound.
能看到我还有多少续航
You can see how much range I have left.
我现在在舒适模式
I'm in chill mode right now.
那里显示的是我的速度
And over there is my speed.
这是一个更新的仪表盘 但依然非常传统
So this is an updated gauge cluster, but very much analog.
这里是你的驻车制动
You've got your parking brake down here.
我现在把脚放在刹车上 准备倒车、行驶和空档
This is, I'll put foot on the brake, reverse, drive, neutral.
而且他们增加了一个带电源的MagSafe充电器
And they've actually added a MagSafe puck
可以给你的MagSafe设备充电
with power just to charge your MagSafe devices.
如果你想用CarPlay
So if you do want CarPlay
想把你的iPhone放在那儿的话
if you want to put your iPhone there
这个小细节加得不错
that is a nice little touch that they've added.
虽然整辆车的其它部分都很复古
Even though the entire rest of this car is super retro
但是你可以在它该放的位置给你的新手机充电
you can have your brand new phone charging right there where it belongs.
但是
but
对
yeah
哇！这里发生的每一件小事都让人感到无比怀旧
oh my god every single little thing happening here is such a throwback
空调这里的这些缺口用于冷却
the air conditioning these notches here for cooling
以及空气流出的地方用于加热
and heating for where the air comes out
显然 所有通风口都是手动的 我们不需要屏幕
obviously all manual vents we're not doing any screens
针对那种情况
for that type of stuff
当然 这里就是你的锁
and of course you have your lock here
打开车门的方式就是这个小玩意儿
and the way you open the door is just this little thing right here
这真酷 我超喜欢！
this is sick I'm loving it.
这边还有几个按钮
Now there's a couple other buttons over here
你应该知道的
that you do want to know about,
尤其是这个带感叹号的按钮
specifically this one with an exclamation point on it
可以将汽车从休闲模式切换到
which switches the car from chill mode
等一下 上面写着 '开我'
hold on it says crank me
因为它让我彻底切换到运动模式 而不是舒适模式
because it wants me to fully turn it on, from chill mode to sport mode.
而这些车的一个特点就是非常个性化
And The thing about these cars is they are so kind of custom
而且每一台都是量身打造的
and like one-off built that you know
舒适模式的能量回收率较高 大约达到65%
there is chill mode which is more regen 65% regen
这模式提供的动力约为三分之二到四分之三
and a you know two-thirds three-quarters of the power
但他们能够进行个性化设置
but they can tailor it
在为你定制汽车时
when they build you the car to be exactly the way you want
运动模式的能量回收较低
sport mode has less regen
能量回收接近20%
closer to 20% regen
但可提供最大动力 所有功能都可定制
but is giving you all of the power again all that can be customized
坐在这样的车里 真让我觉得不可思议
but it's just crazy to me to sit in a car like this
想起以前的车那么小
and knowing that cars used to be so small
你只需伸手就能碰到
that you could reach over
甚至不用完全伸直手臂 就能碰到另一侧
and just Touch the other side without fully extending your arm
以前的车小得多、薄得多
cars used to be so much smaller
这车居然没有安全气囊
so much thinner There's no airbag in this car
不过 挡风玻璃刮水器在这里依然存在
but you've got your windshield wipers here.
转向灯也在这儿
You've got your blinkers over here
一切还是那么熟悉
Things are all still in the familiar places
这一切让我感到无比怀旧
but it's just such a throwback.
真是太棒了！
It's so sick.
这是一种独特的体验 后座也配备了
This is This is a one-of-a-kind Experience you also have your back seats.
别忘了这些哦
Don't forget about those
我的车也有 但几乎没法用
and My car has the same thing, barely usable.
后面最好不要坐成年人
You don't want an adult back there
不过如果你愿意也是可以的
but you could do it if you want to.
不过我先把驾驶体验交给Miles
But I'm going to pass it to Miles for the driving experience
因为内饰我已经给你看过了
because I've shown you the interior.
我已经给你介绍了基本信息
I've shown you the basics.
你可以开200英里 所以Miles
You get 200 miles of driving, so Miles
开起来感觉怎么样？
what's it like to drive?
这辆车的品牌叫做Sacrilege Motors
The brand of this car is Sacrilege Motors
因为这个想法对于很多老派的保时捷爱好者来说
because the idea to a lot of OG Porsche enthusiasts
有人竟然会把这样的车
that someone would take a car like this
而把电动机装进去 简直太疯狂了 对吧？
and put electric motors inside is kind of crazy, right?
我觉得汽车界存在一个大问题
And I think there's this big problem with the car community
很多人觉得它只能是其中一种
where people think it just has to be one
或者另一种 这在某些车辆中尤为明显
or the other for certain types of vehicles.
人们对此感到不满 觉得新法拉利超级跑车怎么能用V6而不是V12呢？
People are upset that the new Ferrari hypercar has a V6 instead of a V12.
但如果你能买得起那辆车
But if you can afford that car
那又有什么理由不去拥有其他12辆V12的车呢？
what's stopping you from owning 12 other cars with a V12?
你可以以同样的角度看待这辆车
You should look at this car the same way.
如果你有将近80万美元的预算
If you have nearly $800,000
或者你还有更多预算可以购买这样的车
or more to spend on a car like this
那有什么理由不把相同的钱
what's also stopping you from spending the equivalent money
花在经典的内燃机保时捷911上呢？
on a classic ICE Porsche 911?
综合以上这些考虑
And so with all that in mind
我觉得这是非常重要的
I think it's important
不要把这辆车和内燃机911放在一起比较
that we don't try to compare this to an ICE 911
因为如果你能负担得起这辆车
because if you can afford this car
你也可以考虑直接去买一辆内燃机964
you can also just get an internal combustion engine 964.
我想说的是 这辆车有
But what I will say... is that what they've done an amazing job at
很多了不起之处
with this car is
确保唯一与911不一样的就是
making sure the only thing that doesn't feel like a 911
就是你车上用的是电动驱动
is the fact that you have electric motors for the drivetrain.
开这辆车的其他每一方面
Literally every other aspect of driving this car
甚至连那种气味
even down to the smells
都能让你感受到经典保时捷911的魅力
is definitely what you would experience with a classic Porsche 911.
转向手感很好 有重量感 连接性强 反馈非常灵敏
The steering field is nice, weighted, connected, super communicative.
需要一点力气才能启动
takes a bit of elbow work to get it going
就像90和80年代的经典保时捷那样
just like a classic Porsche from the 90s, 80s.
显然 它的底盘非常低
It's obviously super low to the ground.
车身非常硬挺
It's very stiff
由于配备了可调三向避震器
because of those three-way adjustable coilovers
稍后我们会详细讨论
that we'll talk about a little bit later.
还有 这辆车非常轻盈
And then the lightness.
这辆车的重量略超过3000磅
This car only weighs just barely over 3,000 pounds
这使得它比大多数
which makes this lighter than most
汽油车都轻
gas powered cars currently on sale today.
动力系统依旧保持传统911的4060重量分布
We also still have the 4060 weight distribution of a traditional 911.
所以无论是重量转移、整体平衡还是操控性
So weight transfer, general balance and handling
都与原版车不相上下
it's all on par with the original car.
不过 当然
But then of course
它的马力达到500马力 扭矩超过500牛米
you've got 500 horsepower, just a little over 500 Newton meters of torque.
我将在这里把数据换算成磅英尺
I'll put the conversion here to pound feet.
这辆车重3000磅 马力500 还是后驱
And so 3000 pounds, 500 horsepower and rear-wheel drive only.
这车加速很快
This thing is quick
说实话 有时候驾驶起来让人有点紧张
and it's quite frankly a little scary at times
就因为它太小了
just because of how small it is.
确实有种经典老车的感觉
It certainly has that OG car feel
就像我们今年在频道中试过的其他车
just like other cars we've had on the channel this year,
比如大众ID Buzz
like the Volkswagen ID Buzz.
像这样的老车真的会让你觉得
Older cars like that really make you feel like,
是的 如果你出错
yeah, if you screw up in this thing
几乎没什么能救你
there's not a lot that's going to save you.
不过 这就是驾驶这种车的乐趣之一
But that's a part of the fun with cars like these,
这些老式保时捷 专为运动设计的跑车
these older Porsches, these older purpose-built sports cars.
某种程度上 缺乏安全性
the lack of safety in a sense
反而增加了体验的刺激感
is almost what adds to the thrill of the experience
这辆车完全没有驾驶辅助
and so in this car there are zero nannies
连牵引力控制系统都没有
you have no traction control system
你只需把方向盘向左转
so you turn the wheel to the left
猛踩油门
and floor it
这辆车立刻侧滑 悬挂系统很有趣,
and you are going sideways the suspension on this car is actually
确实很有意思
really interesting
首先 你会注意到 它的悬挂非常硬
firstly i'm sure you've noticed in this footage that it is pretty stiff uh
车身也很低
it sits very low
所以你会感受到很多路面的颠簸
and so you're gonna feel a lot of those bumps
不过 这要看个人的需求和习惯 能否接受
but It's certainly livable depending on who you are, I guess
以及你居住的区域
and the area you live in.
我住在新泽西
I live in New Jersey
因此 在这里的乘坐舒适性可能不如
so obviously ride comfort is going to always not be the best
其他地方
compared to other places.
不过 它是可调的
But it is adjustable
这是因为它们是三段式可调避震器
and that's because these are three-way adjustable coilovers
Penske Racing制造的
made by Penske Racing.
他们以为超级跑车制造悬挂系统而闻名
And they're known for making setups for, like, you know, supercars,
和运动跑车
sports cars.
所以这个悬挂系统与一些地方的搭配非常相似
And so what this setup is is very similar to something that you'd get in,
比如说一辆GT3 RS
like, a GT3 RS, for example.
这个配置的一个亮点就是配备了远程储液器
One of the killer parts of this setup is having remote reservoirs
您可以打开后备厢看到这些储液器
that you can see by opening the rear hatch of the car.
这些远程储液器
And so you have these remote reservoirs
与车辆底部的主液箱相连
that are connected to the primary fluid tank
液体通过液压管在车底
underneath the car via these hydraulic lines
循环流动
that are feeding fluid back and forth.
这样做的好处之一就是维护更加方便
and so the benefits you're getting is firstly maintenance
只需打开后备厢 您就能轻松访问这些储液器
it's easier to access those reservoirs by just popping over the rear hatch
您只需打开后备厢
but then secondly you're getting easy adjustability
就能轻松调节
by just opening the rear hatch
再调节与油箱连接的旋钮
and adjusting the knobs connected to the reservoir
这让您能够轻松调整驾驶体验
which makes it super easy to tailor your driving experience
适应不同的场景
to whatever scenario you're in
这并不是专为赛道高性能驾驶
this is not necessarily designed to be a super high performance
而设计的车
track vehicle
不过 由于这种配置
but because of this setup
还有车的重量和动力
and the weight and the power
您绝对可以把这辆车带去赛道试驾
you certainly could take this to a track day
而且可能会让很多人大吃一惊
and probably embarrass a lot of folks.
整体上 这款车的乘坐舒适性
And so overall, you're working with ride comfort
比
that's not only better than
原版964车型提供的舒适性
what you would get from an original 964,
而且更具可调性 性能也更卓越
but more adjustable and more capable as well.
这辆车的刹车系统非常优秀
You're also working with a very healthy brake setup in this car.
前部配备六活塞卡钳 后部配备四活塞卡钳
You've got six piston calipers up front, four piston calipers in the rear,
环绕的Brembo刹车盘
big steel Brembo rotors all around.
这样的配置在许多车辆中是常见的
And so a setup like that is what you'd find on a lot of
在过去10年中的高端超级跑车中常见
like high-end supercars from like the past 10 years or so.
不过 刹车的调节非常出色
But the braking modulation is also really nice.
它并不像很多运动汽车那样敏感
It's not super grabby
不会像许多运动汽车那样刺耳
and stabby like a lot of sports cars are known to be.
刹车过程非常平滑而渐进
It's very smooth and gradual
这让日常驾驶变得更加轻松
which makes it a lot easier to live with as a daily driver
如果你有这样的想法
if that's something you wanted to attempt to do.
正如我一开始提到的
So like I mentioned at the beginning
我认为把这个和同年代的911进行比较没有什么意义
I don't think it makes sense to try to compare this as an alternative
与这个时代的NI同款911相比
to the equivalent 911 from this era.
不过 就这一点而言
But even with that in mind
我觉得我们应该将乐趣与这个时代的911进行对比
I do think we should evaluate the fun factor versus a 911 of this era
不是由电动机和电池驱动的
not powered by electric motors and a battery.
我觉得这真得看个人的情况
I think it really depends on who you are.
对某些人来说 没有那种声音就不会有
For some people, not having that noise is just not going to do
任何感觉
anything for you,
无论这车看起来有多令人畏惧或多强大
no matter how scary and how capable the car is overall.
在我看来 我很想为某人买这个
To me, this is something I think I would love to buy for someone
想要驾驶911的感觉的人
who wants the feeling of driving a 911
又不想承担维护责任
without having to deal with all of the maintenance responsibilities
维护这一代911带来的麻烦
that come with maintaining a 911 from this era.
拥有这样一辆车时
When getting a car like this
你就不用担心那些麻烦了
you're not going to have to deal with that sort of stuff.
我觉得学习这些也是一项有趣的挑战
And I think it's also an interesting challenge to try to learn
理解这种瞬时动力输出的汽车
and understand a car with this type of instantaneous power delivery
没有电子牵引力控制辅助
without any of the electronic traction control assists
和其他复杂的系统
and all that fun stuff.
这和学习手动变速的993涡轮增压车
It's certainly different
确实是不同的
than learning to understand a manual transmission 993 turbo
你需要合理地控制换挡时机和油门
where you have to properly time shifts and throttle input with, you know
如果你驾驶的是涡轮增压的911 就要注意涡轮增压带来的动力
the boost of the turbos if you have a turbocharged 911, that sort of stuff.
这绝对是种全新的体验
It's certainly an entirely different experience
无法将其与
one that you can't just compare directly to
内燃机驱动的911进行简单比较
an internal combustion engine powered 911.
开这样一辆车 几乎不可能不感到快乐
I think it's pretty hard to not have fun in a car like this
即使你更喜欢那种8000转的高转速体验
even if you would prefer having, you know, an 8,000 RPM, high revving,
手动变速箱的驾驶乐趣
you know, manual transmission experience.
这并不能取代那种乐趣
This is not a replacement for that
如果你的预算允许
but if you have a budget that allows for it
我觉得这是个很不错的选择
I think it's a pretty cool addition.
我想很多人可能会
It's something that I think a lot of people are going to be
持保留态度
naturally very skeptical about
不过我觉得这也是应该的
but I think it's only right
所以在排除之前 试试也是值得的
that you give it a try before ruling it out.
如果你有这些东西
When you have all these things
有保时捷的媒体中心
when you have the Porsche media center
能体验到保时捷的驾驶感
you have the Porsche steering feel
能闻到保时捷的那种气味
you have the Porsche smell
就像我吉姆叔叔那些老保时捷的味道
it smells like a lot of my Uncle Jim's old Porsches.
这真是太疯狂了
It's actually crazy.
考虑到这一切的时候
When you put all that into consideration
你就会明白为什么价格会这么高
you can understand how you can get to an extremely high price point
因为这些都是手工制作的车
because these are hand-built machines.
这些可不是特斯拉Model 3那样的
These are not Tesla Model 3s where, you know
这里的缝隙就很奇怪
you'll see weird gaps here
还有那些让人感到古怪的不一致
and there and weird quirky inconsistencies.
这确实有种真正的德国车的感觉
This has that real OG German car feel, which is, you know
对于一些人来说 这种感觉是无法用价格来衡量的
it's hard to put a price on that for some people.
我想我真的爱上这个车了
I think I love this thing.
我觉得我已经爱上这款车了
这可能是我在这里测试过的最喜欢的车
This might be my favorite car that we've actually gotten to test here.
这不仅仅是车 更是一种体验
And it's part the car, part the experience.
我又想到了2008年特斯拉跑车的视频
Again, I keep throwing back to that 2008 Tesla Roadster video
自从第一款特斯拉跑车以来
how far the technology has come since the original Tesla Roadster,
电池的密度
the battery density
你能获得多远的续航
how much range you get
充电速度快得惊人
how fast they charge.
我还没来得及给你看呢
I didn't even show you.
在结束前 我给你看看最后一件事
I should show you one last thing before I wrap this up.
这个充电方式其实挺简单的
How you charge this is actually kind of really intuitive.
你只需抓住它往外拉
You just grab this and pull.
然后这个就打开了
And this opens.
你的充电口就在这里
And there's your charge port right here.
CCS
CCS.
直接把它放进去就行
Pop it right in there.
就像你想的那样 这实际上就像一个油箱
Like you would expect that to be a sort of a gas tank
但他们考虑得非常周全
but they've thought of everything.
不过我非常喜欢这个项目
But I love this project
因为这是一辆显然来自80年代的经典老车
because it's just such an obviously original, OG-looking car from the 80s,
那经典的外形
the classic shape.
我觉得没有人会对这个911的造型不喜欢
I don't think anyone's ever not liked the shape of this 911
而它恰好有我所熟悉的
but then it just has what I'm familiar with
那就是我熟悉的电动驾驶体验
which is the electric driving experience
而且这方面做得非常出色
and kind of does it really well.
这是一辆极具乐趣的车
This is an ultimate fun car.
我真心喜欢它
I love it.
如果你想了解 可以在下方找到链接
I'll leave a link below if you want to check them out.
看这个视频的人不会去买这样的车
Probably nobody who actually watches this is going to go buy one of these
但这绝对是最牛逼的体验之一
but it's one of the sickest things ever
我很高兴能体验到这个
and I'm glad I got to experience it.
希望能再体验一次
Hopefully I get to try this again.
好的 谢谢大家的观看！
All right, thanks for watching.
下次见！
Catch you in the next one.
保持平安！
Peace.